A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18 FA290
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1; 171.6 Cubic Feet; 390 boxes, 532 microfilm reels
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Evaluating and Reports), 1952-1954 (Box 373, Folder 3583)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Evaluating and Reports), 1952-1954 (Box 373, Folder 3584)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Supplementary Material), 1952-1954 (Box 373, Folder 3585)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Supplementary Material), 1952-1954 (Box 373, Folder 3586)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Supplementary Material), 1952-1954 (Box 373, Folder 3587)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Supplementary Material), 1952-1954 (Box 374, Folder 3588)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Supplementary Material), 1952-1954 (Box 374, Folder 3589)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Supplementary Material), 1952-1954 (Box 374, Folder 3590)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Supplementary Material), 1952-1954 (Box 374, Folder 3591)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase I Supplementary Material), 1952-1954 (Box 374, Folder 3592)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase II Reports), 1953-1954 (Box 374, Folder 3593)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase II Reports), 1953-1954 (Box 374, Folder 3594)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase IIA Laboratory), 1954 (Box 374, Folder 3595)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase IIA Laboratory), 1954 (Box 375, Folder 3596)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase IIA Lecture), 1954 (Box 375, Folder 3597)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase IIA Lecture), 1954 (Box 375, Folder 3598)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase IIA Lecture), 1954 (Box 375, Folder 3599)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase IIA Lecture), 1954 (Box 375, Folder 3600)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Phase III), 1955 (Box 375, Folder 3601)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Supplementary Reports), 1951-1954 (Box 375, Folder 3602)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Supplementary Reports), 1951-1954 (Box 375, Folder 3603)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Supplementary Reports), 1951-1954 (Box 375, Folder 3604)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Supplementary Reports), 1951-1956 (Box 376, Folder 3605)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Supplementary Reports), 1951-1956 (Box 376, Folder 3606)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Supplementary Reports), 1951-1956 (Box 376, Folder 3607)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Health Science Library (ME&CH), 1963-1969 (Box 376, Folder 3608)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Leukemia Study, 1937-1947 (Box 376, Folder 3609)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Leukemia Study, 1937-1947 (Box 376, Folder 3610)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Leukemia Study, 1937-1947 (Box 376, Folder 3611)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Leukemia Study - Financial Data, 1939-1944 (Box 376, Folder 3612)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Leukemia Study - Financial Data, 1939-1944 (Box 376, Folder 3613)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Leukemia Study - Financial Data, 1945-1947 (Box 377, Folder 3614)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Mechanism of Heart Failure Study, 1938-1944 (Box 377, Folder 3615)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Mechanism of Heart Failure Study, 1938-1944 (Box 377, Folder 3616)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Mechanism of Heart Failure Study - Financial Data, 1938-1944 (Box 377, Folder 3617)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Mechanism of Heart Failure Study - Financial Data, 1938-1944 (Box 377, Folder 3618)
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Survey of the Work of the Child Research Council (MR), 1953-1955 (Box 377, Folder 3619)
  - White-William Foundation - General Support, 1921-1924 (Box 377, Folder 3620)
  - White-William Foundation - General Support, 1921-1924 (Box 377, Folder 3621)
  - University of Wisconsin (Enzyme Institute) - Integrated Enzyme Action Study (MR), 1948-1953 (Box 377, Folder 3622)
  - University of Wisconsin (Enzyme Institute) - Integrated Enzyme Action Study (MR), 1948-1953 (Box 377, Folder 3623)
  - University of Wisconsin (Enzyme Institute) - Integrated Enzyme Action Study - Financial Data (MR), 1948-1951 (Box 378, Folder 3624)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy - Annual Membership, 1980-1982 (Box 378, Folder 3625)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy - Program to Change Patterns of Sex Discrimination in Organized Philanthropy, 1978-1981 (Box 378, Folder 3626)
  - Worchester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Biological Role of Steroids (MR), 1953-1965 (Box 378, Folder 3627)
  - Worchester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Biological Role of Steroids (MR), 1953-1965 (Box 378, Folder 3628)
  - Worchester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Biological Role of Steroids (MR), 1953-1965 (Box 378, Folder 3629)
  - Worchester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Biological Role of Steroids (MR), 1953-1965 (Box 378, Folder 3630)
  - Worchester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Biological Role of Steroids (MR), 1953-1965 (Box 378, Folder 3631)
  - Worchester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Blood Studies in Relation to Psychoses (MR), 1959-1966 (Box 378, Folder 3632)
  - Worchester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Blood Studies in Relation to Psychoses (MR), 1959-1966 (Box 378, Folder 3633)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force, 1978-1980 (Box 379, Folder 3634)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force, 1978-1980 (Box 379, Folder 3635)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force, 1978-1980 (Box 379, Folder 3636)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force, 1978-1980 (Box 379, Folder 3637)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force, 1978-1980 (Box 379, Folder 3638)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force, 1978-1980 (Box 379, Folder 3639)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force, 1978-1980 (Box 379, Folder 3640)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force - Conference Proceedings, April 18, 1979 (Box 379, Folder 3641)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force - Highlights of the Literature, 1978-1979 (Box 379, Folder 3642)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force - Highlights of the Literature, 1978-1979 (Box 379, Folder 3643)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force - Highlights of the Literature, 1979 (Box 380, Folder 3644)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force - Plans and Progress, 1978 (Box 380, Folder 3645)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force - Proposal, October 12, 1979 (Box 380, Folder 3646)
  - Work in American Institute - Improvement of Employer, Union and Government Accommodation of an Aging American Work Force - Publications, 1978-1980 (Box 380, Folder 3647)
  - Work in American Institute - Promotion of New Patterns of Work That Benefit Employees and Increase Productivity, 1979-1983 (Box 380, Folder 3648)
  - Work in American Institute - Promotion of New Patterns of Work That Benefit Employees and Increase Productivity, 1979-1983 (Box 380, Folder 3649)
  - Work in American Institute - Promotion of New Patterns of Work That Benefit Employees and Increase Productivity, 1979-1983 (Box 380, Folder 3650)
  - Work in American Institute - Promotion of New Patterns of Work That Benefit Employees and Increase Productivity, 1979-1983 (Box 380, Folder 3651)
  - Work in American Institute - Promotion of New Patterns of Work That Benefit Employees and Increase Productivity, 1979-1983 (Box 380, Folder 3652)
  - World Council of Churches - Consultation on Genetics and the Quality of Life, 1972-1975 (Box 381, Folder 3653)
  - World Federation for Medical Education, Inc. - General Support, 1977-1981 (Box 381, Folder 3654)
  - World Federation for Medical Education, Inc. - General Support, 1977-1981 (Box 381, Folder 3655)
  - World Federation for Mental Health - General Support, 1949-1953 (Box 381, Folder 3656)
  - World Federation for Mental Health - General Support, 1949-1953 (Box 381, Folder 3657)
  - World Medical Association, Inc. - Education Fund - Contribution to the Fourth World Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 381, Folder 3658)
  - Yale University - Center for the Study of Human Genetics, 1974-1981 (Box 381, Folder 3659)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood (MR), 1950-1952 (Box 381, Folder 3660)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood (MR), 1950-1952 (Box 381, Folder 3661)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood (MR), 1952-1953 (Box 382, Folder 3662)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood (MR), 1952-1953 (Box 382, Folder 3663)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development (MR), 1954-1960 (Box 382, Folder 3664)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development (MR), 1954-1960 (Box 382, Folder 3665)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development (MR), 1954-1960 (Box 382, Folder 3666)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development (MR), 1954-1960 (Box 382, Folder 3667)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development (MR), 1954-1960 (Box 382, Folder 3668)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development - Financial Data (MR), 1950-1952 (Box 382, Folder 3669)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development - Manuscript (MR), 1953-1959 (Box 382, Folder 3670)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development - Manuscript (MR), 1953-1959 (Box 382, Folder 3671)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development - Manuscript (MR), 1953-1959 (Box 382, Folder 3672)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development - New Family Correspondence (MR), 1957-1959 (Box 382, Folder 3673)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Regional Center for Service, Education and Research in Problems of Early Childhood Development (ME&CH), 1972-1978 (Box 383, Folder 3674)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Regional Center for Service, Education and Research in Problems of Early Childhood Development (ME&CH), 1972-1978 (Box 383, Folder 3675)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Regional Center for Service, Education and Research in Problems of Early Childhood Development - Supplementary Material (ME&CH), 1972-1977 (Box 383, Folder 3676)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Regional Center for Service, Education and Research in Problems of Early Childhood Development - Supplementary Material (ME&CH), 1972-1977 (Box 383, Folder 3677)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Regional Center for Service, Education and Research in Problems of Early Childhood Development - Supplementary Material (ME&CH), 1972-1977 (Box 383, Folder 3678)
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Regional Center for Service, Education and Research in Problems of Early Childhood Development - Supplementary Material (ME&CH), 1972-1977 (Box 383, Folder 3679)
  - Yale University - Construction of New Science Laboratory, 1954-1955 (Box 383, Folder 3680)
  - Yale University (Department of Sociology) - Experimental Graduate Training Program in the Social Aspects of Medicine (ME), 1953-1958 (Box 383, Folder 3681)
  - Yale University (Department of Sociology) - Experimental Graduate Training Program in the Social Aspects of Medicine (ME), 1953-1958 (Box 383, Folder 3682)
  - Yale University (Department of Sociology) - Experimental Graduate Training Program in the Social Aspects of Medicine (ME), 1953-1958 (Box 383, Folder 3683)
  - Yale University (Department of Sociology) - Experimental Graduate Training Program in the Social Aspects of Medicine (ME), 1953-1958 (Box 383, Folder 3684)
  - Yale University (Department of Sociology) - Experimental Graduate Training Program in the Social Aspects of Medicine (ME), 1959-1965 (Box 384, Folder 3685)
  - Yale University - Designing a Program in Human Biology and Ecology (ME), 1950-1953 (Box 384, Folder 3686)
  - Yale University - Designing a Program in Human Biology and Ecology (ME), 1950-1953 (Box 384, Folder 3687)
  - Yale University - Fundamental Reappraisal of the University's Medical Program (ME&CH), 1966-1974 (Box 384, Folder 3688)
  - Yale University (Law School) - Graduate Education and Research Program in Law, Science and Medicine (ME&CH), 1972-1977 (Box 384, Folder 3689)
  - Yale University (Law School) - Graduate Education and Research Program in Law, Science and Medicine (ME&CH), 1972-1977 (Box 384, Folder 3690)
  - Yale University - Memorial for Edward S. Harkness, 1952-1956 (Box 384, Folder 3691)
  - Yale University - Memorial for Edward S. Harkness, 1952-1956 (Box 384, Folder 3692)
  - Yale University - Memorial for Edward S. Harkness, 1952-1956 (Box 384, Folder 3693)
  - Yale University - Mental Hygiene College Conference, 1926-1927 (Box 384, Folder 3694)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Auditorium Construction (ME&CH), 1958-1964 (Box 384, Folder 3695)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Committee on Medical Affairs, 1972-1974 (Box 384, Folder 3696)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma (ME&CH), 1968-1978 (Box 385, Folder 3697)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma (ME&CH), 1968-1978 (Box 385, Folder 3698)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma (ME&CH), 1968-1978 (Box 385, Folder 3699)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma (ME&CH), 1968-1978 (Box 385, Folder 3700)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma (ME&CH), 1968-1978 (Box 385, Folder 3701)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Communications System for Emergency Medical Services for the New Haven Area (ME&CH), June 11, 1971 (Box 385, Folder 3702)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Emergency Medical Communications System for South Central Connecticut (ME&CH), November 12, 1971 (Box 385, Folder 3703)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Financial Data (ME&CH), April 2, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 3704)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Financial Data (ME&CH), April 2, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 3705)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Financial Data (ME&CH), April 2, 1969 (Box 386, Folder 3706)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Financial Data (ME&CH), April 2, 1969 (Box 386, Folder 3707)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Financial Data (ME&CH), April 2, 1969 (Box 386, Folder 3708)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Financial Data (ME&CH), April 2, 1969 (Box 386, Folder 3709)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Progress Report (ME&CH), October 18, 1974 (Box 386, Folder 3710)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Questions Concerning the Yale-New Haven Medical Center (ME&CH), March 12, 1969 (Box 386, Folder 3711)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Study and Analysis of Emergency Medical Services in Connecticut (ME&CH), July 23, 1971 (Box 386, Folder 3712)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Study and Analysis of Emergency Medical Services in Connecticut (ME&CH), April 5, 1973 (Box 386, Folder 3713)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Study and Analysis of Emergency Medical Services in Connecticut (ME&CH), April 5, 1973 (Box 387, Folder 3714)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma - Survey Report (ME&CH), October 14-17, 1968 (Box 387, Folder 3715)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, 1979-1982 (Box 387, Folder 3716)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Mental Hygiene - Institute of Human Behavior, 1927-1935 (Box 387, Folder 3717)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Mental Hygiene - Mental Hygiene Work, 1925-1929 (Box 387, Folder 3718)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Mental Hygiene - Mental Hygiene Work, 1925-1929 (Box 387, Folder 3719)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Mental Hygiene - Mental Hygiene Work, 1925-1929 (Box 387, Folder 3720)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Mental Hygiene - Mental Hygiene Work, 1929-1931 (Box 388, Folder 3721)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Mental Hygiene - Mental Hygiene Work (Minutes and Monthly Reports), 1926-1932 (Box 388, Folder 3722)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Mental Hygiene - Mental Hygiene Work (Minutes and Monthly Reports), 1926-1932 (Box 388, Folder 3723)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Psychiatry, 1947-1955 (Box 388, Folder 3724)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Psychiatry, 1947-1955 (Box 388, Folder 3725)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Psychiatry, 1947-1955 (Box 388, Folder 3726)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Department of Psychiatry - Financial Data, 1949-1951 (Box 388, Folder 3727)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Establishment of the Division of Cell Biology, 1971-1977 (Box 388, Folder 3728)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Etiology of Vascular Disease, 1938-1939 (Box 388, Folder 3729)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Etiology of Vascular Disease, 1939-1946 (Box 389, Folder 3730)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Etiology of Vascular Disease, 1939-1946 (Box 389, Folder 3731)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Etiology of Vascular Disease, 1939-1946 (Box 389, Folder 3732)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Etiology of Vascular Disease, 1939-1946 (Box 389, Folder 3733)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Etiology of Vascular Disease - Financial Data, 1938-1946 (Box 389, Folder 3734)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Etiology of Vascular Disease - Financial Data, 1938-1946 (Box 389, Folder 3735)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Experimental Study of Cardiovascular-Renal Disease, 1946-1948 (Box 389, Folder 3736)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Experimental Study of Cardiovascular-Renal Disease, 1946-1948 (Box 389, Folder 3737)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Experimental Study of Cardiovascular-Renal Disease, 1948-1952 (Box 390, Folder 3738)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Experimental Study of Cardiovascular-Renal Disease - Financial Data, 1946-1948 (Box 390, Folder 3739)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Laboratory of Clinical Investigation, 1961-1967 (Box 390, Folder 3740)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Longitudinal Study of the Medical School Admissions Process, 1975-1981 (Box 390, Folder 3741)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Longitudinal Study of the Medical School Admissions Process, 1975-1981 (Box 390, Folder 3742)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - New Haven Hospital, 1921-1922 (Box 390, Folder 3743)
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Nine School Consortium Joint Planning Project, 1971-1975 (Box 390, Folder 3744)
  - Yale University - Ten-Year, Multidisciplinary Study of Private, Non-Profit Institutions and Organizations, 1976-1981 (Box 390, Folder 3745)
  - Yale University - Ten-Year, Multidisciplinary Study of Private, Non-Profit Institutions and Organizations, 1976-1981 (Box 390, Folder 3746)
  - Yale University - Ten-Year, Multidisciplinary Study of Private, Non-Profit Institutions and Organizations, 1976-1981 (Box 390, Folder 3747)
  - York College (The City University of New York) - Summer Science Program for High School Students (1979), 1979-1981 (Box 390, Folder 3748)
- Grants, 2; 4.4 Cubic Feet
  - Affiliated Hospital Center - Study of Center for Cost Effective Care, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series 18.2 Brigham and Women's Hospital, Box 2, Folders 9-14.
  - Affiliated Hospital Center - Study of Center for Cost Effective Care, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)